Hello, developers, and welcome to exercise number 59.
We are asked to write a function that Append notes to the injured list appending A. A. is adding the
note at the end of the list, so we need to allow a function variety function that allow us and the
user to insert notes at the end of their linked list.
So for that, we go to the Methods Here Methods section and we start making the method so I will create
public void.
Called End.
I need from you to post the video and think about it.
The lecture before that in videos before demonstrates how to offend all of these exercises.
And we are resolving them in a real program in order to allow you to take it to be self-satisfied and
and confidence in all your interviews and exercises in universities.
So please write these down and get notes from them.
And I need from you to continue contributing with our letters by sending your solution in the comments
below in order to discuss and see if you have any misunderstanding of topics.
So in order to attend, we start by entering new data.
And we start by creating the note.
So how to create the note?
We start by.
This is the first step.
This is exercise No.
59.
Note, this is the first step in creating the note.
Nodes new node.
This is the direct behind, it's new, and we passed the data that we have passed from the arguments
and we create inside the constructor, pass it to new data.
OK,
node less equal to ahead.
No.
We are going this will be used in step number four.
OK, so Nunez.
Second step is going.
Then you know, there's going to be the last making next of it as not making their newly newly new nodes
as last know by making, you know, the next equal to nothing.
OK.
As I told you, the last note will be referencing to the next breath as not the third step is.
If the linked list is empty, then make the note as hat check,
check for hat.
If had equal equal to none.
Then we start buying new note.
You know, the previous
sorry proved equal to none.
OK.
And had equal to, you know,
then return if we have the first had the first note is had and we are checking if had not had that previous
equal to none and had then create had equal to, you know, and then right.
OK.
This is checking for that now else.
Let's see.
While the last dot next does not equal to none.
Then you go and make the last equal to the last thought next.
OK, so we are traversing until the last known finding.
Finding the last note.
OK.
No change the next of the last note to become then last note that next equal to that new note.
So fifth step is change the next of last note by making last dot next equal to new No.
OK, because there is a new node that have been inserted after the last node in the Met in the list
that before appending.
OK.
And then make the last note as a previous of the new No.
So the six step number six as make last node as previous of new knowledge new node that the previous
equal to the last.
OK, this is how a pending works.
Now let's test it in the main activity and we will.
At the end, or we can make here the Alan Dot app, and I will append a note that contains number four.
That's Ron Nancy.
It is have been added at the last.
Yes.
If we print forward way, we have one, two, three and four four is not and in that in here we are
not pushing for is added at the last note and by proof, the last note would be printed at the first
note.
If we are printing the list, the reversely and there we go, we have solved this exercise.
And it's very common and very frequently ask exercise in universities.